Guide to the Franz R. and Kathryn M. Stenzel Research Files on Western American Art
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Research Files for an Unpublished Book on Western Art, 1859-1997; Series V; 9.66; (23 boxes)
  - RESEARCH FILES
    - Artist Information Index
      - "Not Northwest" File
        - Christy - Currier, 1951-65, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 511)
          Crasby, George R.
          Cumming, William
          Currier, Edmund Wilson
        - Dahlager - Douglas, David, 1962-74, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 512)
          Dahlager, Jules
          Dahlgren, Carl
          Dahlgreen, Charles W.
          Daingenfield, Elliot
          Dalrymple, Louis
          Davis, George Wesley
          Davis, Herndon
          Dawson, Arthur
          Deas, Charles
          Delaney, Charles W.
          Delano, Gerard Curtis
          DeLappe, Phyllis
          Demaris, Walter
          Dillingham, John E.
          Dodge, William de Leftwich
          Donahue, Vic
          Douglas, David
        - Douglas, Edward Bruce - Dyck, 1960-63, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 513)
          Douglas, Edward Bruce
          Drake, A. C.
          DuMond, Frank Vincent
          Dumond, Frederick Melville
          Dunn, Harvey
          Dunn, Lyndle G.
          Dunnell, John Henry
          Duveneck, Frank
          Dyck, Paul
          Includes illustrated article
          on Harvey Dunn, "The Prairie is
          My Homeland" in September 1960
          issue of Together
        - Eakins - Eyerly, 1963-68, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 514)
          Eakins, Thomas
          Earle, Laurence Carmichael
          Eaton, Charles Henry
          Eccles, G. B.
          Edmonds, Francis
          Ellis, Fremont F.
          Ellsworth, Clarence Arthur
          Elston, Lafe
          Englebert, Joseph E.
          Erb, J.
          Esdaile, J.
          Eskridge, Robert Lee
          "Euryalus"
          Evans, J. G.
          Ewart, Peter
          Eyerly, Ray
        - Fangel - Fletcher, 1963-71, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 515)
          Fangel, Henry Guy
          Farm, G.
          Farquar, George
          Farquar, J. T.
          Faulkner, Barry
          Fechin, Nicholai
          Fellows, Fred
          Fenderich, Charles
          Fiore, Rosario
          Firfires, Nicholas S.
          Fish, H. R.
          Fisher, Hugo Antoine
          Fisher, Hugo Melville
          Fletcher, Martha J
        - Ford - Frerichs, 1955-67, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 516)
          Ford, Henry Chapman
          Forsyth, William
          Forsythe, Clyde
          Fortune, Euphemia Charleton
          Fournier, Alex Jean
          Franklin, Dwight
          Fraundorf, R.
          Frerichs, W. A. C.
          Includes issue of Quarterly Los Angeles County Museum History
          Division Issue, Vol. 12, No. 3,
          Fall 1955 with article by Dwight
          Franklin, inscribed to Stenzel
          by Franklin
        - Frost - Fussell, 1938-67, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 517)
          Frost, Arthur Burdette
          Fuechsel, Hermann
          Fuller, F. V.
          Fussell, Charles Lewis
        - Garver - Gruppe, 1963-67, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 518)
          Garver, W. L., Jr.
          Gellert, Samuel Morse
          Gibson, Charles Dana
          Gilbert, Carrie M.
          Godart, Jules
          Goddard, G. H.
          Gomez, Marco A.
          Grady, William H.
          Greatorex, Eliza
          Greatorex, Kathleen
          Greenfield, Warren
          Gruppe, Charles Paul
        - Hafen - Hayes, 1960-68, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 519)
          Hafen, John
          Hallidie, A. W.
          Hahn, Karl Wilhelm
          Hall, Carl
          Hall, Virgil
          Hamman, Joë
          Hamel, William
          Hansbrough, M. B. C.
          Hansen, Armin C.
          Harkness, Lars
          Harmer, Alexander F.
          Harmon, Charles
          Harpe, Joseph de la
          Harrison, Mark Rogent
          Hartley, Jonathan S.
          Harvey, Edward
          Harwood, Burt
          Hasch, Karl
          Hassett, W. R.
          Hassman, Carl
          Hausrath, F. E.
          Hawthorne, C. W.
          Hayes, Edward G.
          Includes article by Edward G.
          Hayes, "ZA Roundup" from The Colorado Magazine summer 1964,
          Vol. 41, No. 3
        - Healy - Hope, 1943-75, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 520)
          Healy, George Peter Alexander
          Heap, Gwynn Harris
          Heger, Joseph
          Heikka, Earle Erik
          Helmi, Juvonen
          Hennings, E. Martin
          Henry, Edward Lampson
          Heramcourt, W. V.
          Herget, Herbert
          Heriot, George
          Herr, Lucy Deere
          Herzberg, Paul
          Hess, J. N.
          Hicks, Edward
          Higgins, Victor
          Hilton, W. M.
          Hinchley, William J.
          Hittell, Charles J.
          Hofsten, J.
          Hope, [----?]
        - House - Hyams, 1963-74, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 521)
          House, F.
          Houser, John
          Howe, William A.
          Howland, Alfred Cornelius
          Hoyt, Nellie
          Hudson, Grace Carpenter
          Huntington, Anna Vaughan Hyatt
          Hutchens, Frank Townsend
          Hyams, Addie F.
        - Ives - Jeppenson, 1964-74, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 522)
          Ives, Percy
          Ivey, J.
          Jackson, Harry
          Jackson, Hewitt R.
          Jackson, W.
          Jeppenson, Sam
        - Kean - Kunath, 1962-65, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 523)
          Kean, Edmund A.
          Kegg, George W.
          Keller, F.
          Kemeys, Edward
          Kern, Benjamin Jordan
          Kern, RIchard Hovenden
          Key, John Ross
          Kimball, E. O.
          King, Charles B.
          King, G. W.
          King, Len H.
          Kirkpatrick, James
          Kirkwood, Mary B.
          Knight, Augusta
          Koehler, Robert
          Koehn, Max
          Kollm, Max W.
          Kollner, August
          Koppel, Charles
          Krause, E.
          Krieghoff, Cornelius
          Kuemmel, Cornelia A.
          Kummer, Julius Hermann
          Kunath, Oscar A.
        - Lange - Lovett, 1964-69, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 524)
          Lange, [----?]
          Lanman, Charles
          Lea, Tom
          Learned, Harry
          Lee, Joseph
          Lee, W. R.
          Leighton, Kathryn
          Leutze, Emanuel
          Lewis, Henry
          Lewis, James Otto
          Linn, Frank
          Long, Stanley M.
          Lord, John Keast
          Lotave, Carl
          Lotz, Matilda
          Lougheed, Robert
          Love, C. Waldo
          Lovett, R.
        - MacMonnies - Meuthman, 1963-67, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 525)
          MacMonnies, Frederick William
          Macy, William M.
          Martin, Fletcher
          Maryott, MIles
          Mathew, Arthur F.
          Maurer, Louis
          Maurer, Oscar
          Maybelle, Claudius
          Mayer, Frank B.
          McArdle, H. A.
          McComas, Francis John
          McCormick, Evelyn M.
          McCosh, Anne K.
          McGie, Kate
          Mechau, Frank
          Meeker, Joseph Rusling
          Menchaca, Juan
          Mendelli, Antonio
          Metzger, Henry
          Meuthman, W.
          Includes illustrated exhibition
          catalog of paintings and drawings
          by Frank Mechau by the Amon Carter
          Museum of Western Art, 1967
        - Millet - Moser, 1927-65, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 526)
          Millet, Francis Davis
          M'Ilvaine, William
          Mitchell, Alfred R.
          Mitchell, Arthur Roy
          Mitchell, John Ames
          Moeller, Olaf
          Moessner, Thomas T.
          Montgomery, Alfred
          Moore, Lucia Wilkins
          Moran, Edward
          Moran, John
          Moran, Percy
          Moser, James Henry
        - Nagel - Otter, 1951-73, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 527)
          Nagel, Herman F.
          Nahl, Perham W.
          Narjot, Ernest
          Neseman, Enno
          Nicholls, Rhoda Holmes
          Nicoli, Antonio
          Nimy, Buck
          Nogelburg, Johannes
          Norieri, August
          Nourse, Elizabeth
          Oakes, A. T.
          O'Brien, George
          Oldfield, Fred
          Olstad, Einar
          Onderdonk, Julian
          Onderdonk, Robert Jenkins
          Otter, Thomas
        - Padleford - Purrington, 1957-63, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 528)
          Padleford, Morgan
          Pages, Jules Eugene
          Paget, Maude C.
          Parrish, Annabelle Hutchinson
          Parrish, Maxfield
          Parrish, Thomas
          Parrot, Walter
          Parson, Sheldon
          Patty, Elsie Cave
          Peel, Paul
          Pendorf, [----?]
          Penman, G. W.
          Perry, E. F.
          Peters, Les
          Peterson, Clara Glove
          Phillips, Bert
          Phipps, William H.
          Platt, G. W.
          Podchernikoff, Alexis M.
          Pomarede, Leon
          Pope, Alexander
          Porter, Elmer Johnson
          Post, Charles Johnson
          Post, William Kintzing
          Powell, Asa Lynn "Ace"
          Powell, Lucien Whitin
          Portland, Ferdinand
          Provonsha, [----?]
          Purrington, James G.
        - Raschen - Ryan, 1958-67, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 529)
          Raschen, Henry
          Ray, Man
          Read, Henry
          Reaugh, Frank
          Redmond, Granville S.
          Remington, S. J.
          Reuterdahl, Henry
          Reynolds, Charles
          Rhodes, G. M.
          Rice, Fred Sanford
          Richardson, A. J.
          Richardt, Joachim Ferdinand
          Rindisbacher, Peter
          Rinehart, F. A.
          Rivas, J.
          Robertson, Thayne
          Robinson, Regina Dorland
          Roether, Paulus
          Rollins, Jasper
          Rolshoven, Julius C.
          Rorphuro, J. T.
          Ross, Thomas
          Rothermel, Peter Frederick
          Rothery, Albert
          Rowe, Clarence R.
          Rudolph, Harold
          Ryan, John
          Includes exhibition catalog of
          paintings by Regina Dorland
          Robinson, University of Oregon,
          1958
        - Saintin - Schott, 1905-67, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 530)
          Saintin, Jules Emile
          Sandor, Mathias
          Sauerwein, Frank Peter
          Say, Thomas
          Schindler, Antonio Zeno
          Schmedtgen, William Herman
          Schmitt, Paul A.
          Scholl, Louis
          Schoolcraft, Henry
          Schoonover, Frank
          Schope, Irvin
          Schott, Arthur
        - Schouler - Smith, Dan, 1964-67, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 531)
          Schouler, Willard C.
          Schuchard, Carl
          Schultz, J. B.
          Schultz, James Willard
          Schwiering, Conrad
          Scriver, Robert
          Sebron, Hippolyte
          Seymour, Samuel
          Shapleigh, Frank Henry
          Sheffers, Peter Winthrop
          Shrady, Henry Merwin
          Shriner, Henry Gobble
          Sindelar, Charles
          Sloan, [----?]
          Smellie, R.
          Smillie, George Berry
          Smillie, James David
          Smith, Cecil
          Smith, Dan
        - Smith, E. Boyd - Sylvester, 1963-73, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 532)
          Smith, E. Boyd
          Smith, Marshall J.
          Smith, Wallace
          Smyth, William
          Snider, W. S.
          Snook, John, Jr.
          Somers, Charles A.
          Sparks, Will
          Speer, J. A.
          Stackpole, Ralph
          Standing, William
          Standing Bear, Luther
          Stefan, Ross
          Stevens, I. I.
          Stevens, M. L.
          Stobart, John
          Stole, John
          Streight, Howard A.
          Stull, Henry
          Sully, Thomas
          Suydan, E.
          Swain, C. H.
          Swinnerton, James E.
          Sylvester, Frederick Oakes
        - Taft - Turner-Turner, 1963-68, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 533)
          Taft, Lorado
          Talcott, Allan Butter
          Tallant, Richard
          Taylor, James E.
          Teague, Donald
          Teater, Archie
          Tensfield, J.
          Thomas, Reynolds
          Thornton, J. Quinn
          Tiffany, Louis C.
          Tonk, Ernst
          Tracy, John M.
          Trego Jonathan K.
          Trego, William J.
          Trotter, Newbold Hough
          Troubetzcoy, Paul
          Tschudy, Herbert Bolivar
          Turner, George R.
          Turner-Turner, J.
        - Ufer - Ward, 1963-74, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 534)
          Ufer, Walter
          Vallejo, N. P.
          Van Cise, Monona
          Vanderhoff, Charles A.
          VanRyder, Jack
          Von Beckhe, H. V. A.
          Von Kittlitz, Frederick A.
          Von Schmidt, Allexey W.
          Von Schmidt, Harold
          Walke, Henry N.
          Walker, James
          Walker, William Acken
          Wall, Bernhard
          Walter, [----?]
          Wandersforde, Ivan Buckingham
          Ward, Charles Caleb
          Ward, Edmund F.
          Ward, J. Stephen
          Ward, John Quincy Adams
        - Warren - Wild, 1962-68, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 535)
          Warren, A. R.
          Watt, William G.
          Waud, Alfred R.
          Waugh, Frederick Judd
          Weber, Walter Alois
          Webster, Frederick
          Weggeland, Danquart Anthon
          Weinman, Adolph Alexander
          Wheeler, Hughlette
          Wheeler, William R.
          Widforss, Gunner
          Wieghorst, Olaf
          Wild, John Caspar
        - Wiles - Yeager, 1964-73, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 536)
          Wiles, Irving R.
          Wiles, Lemuel Maynard
          Wiley, Lucia
          Willard, Eugene S., Mrs.
          Williams, F. W.
          Williamson, Hunter
          Williamson, John
          Willis, R. C.
          Wilsch, F. G.
          Wimar, Karl Ferdinand
          Winingar, Jess
          Winter, George
          Woodside, J. A.
          Worral, Henry
          Wyeth, N. C.
          Wyttenbach, E.
          Yeager, Walter Rush
    - Other Subject Files
      - "Artists by States." Typescript and holograph notes, 1951, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 537-540)
      - "California artists [and organizations]" Printed material and holograph notes, 1963-71, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 541-543)
      - "Canadian Artists and Art Organizations." Holograph and typescript notes (Box 30, Folder 544)
      - "Lithographers and Oregon Country items." Correspondence, printed material, holograph notes, 1913-74, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 545-547)
        Includes artist information files
        for: Joseph Becker, Otto Becker,
        Charles C. Kuchel, Emil Dressel, Eli
        Sheldon Glover, Edward W. Lange, with
        a photograph of Otto Becker, and The Diary of Eli Sheldon Glover October- December, 1875. Transcribed from the original by The Oregon Historical Records Survey Project, Division of Professional and Service Projects, Works Projects Administration,
        Portland, Oregon, 1940
      - Malaspina Expedition artwork. Notes and correspondence with Warren L. Cook, 1974, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 548)
      - "Montana and Washington" [artists]. Correspondence, holograph notes, 1965, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 549-550)
      - "Northwest Art Schools and Museums." Holograph notes (Box 30, Folder 551)
      - "Oregon Country Prints." Correspondence, holograph notes, copy photographs, 1939-75, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 552-553)
      - "Oregon Region Illustrators." Printed material, correspondence, holograph notes, 1973, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 554)
        Includes brief artist information
        files for: Jules B. Dahlager, Warren
        Dahler, John R. Byng, William Edgar
        Spader, Alexander Schilling
      - "Portland and Northwest Art Activity." Typescript and holograph notes, printed material and correspondence, 1960-66, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 555-558)
        sheets for artists of the area
      - "Region Art." Typescript notes, correspondence, and printed material, 1964, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 559)
      - "Visitors & Paintbrushes." Typescript and holograph notes, arranged by chapter, 1965, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 560-561)
      - "Voyages to 1800." Holograph and typescript notes, printed material, correspondence, 1960-69, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 562-564)
      - Washington Artists. Typescript notes, corrected, 1961, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 565)
      - Miscellaneous research notes, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 566-566a)
  - WRITINGS
    - Introduction
      - Holograph draft, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 567)
      - Holograph and typescript drafts (Box 31, Folder 568)
      - Typescript drafts, 1960, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 569-570)
        Includes "Why This Book Should Have
        Been Written and Published" and
        "Illustrations and Illustrators,"
        possibly meant as preliminary
        chapters
    - "1778-1805. Touring Artists by Sea"
      - Typescript draft, corrected, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 571)
    - "1778-1805."
      - Full title: "1778-1805. Competition for the Northwest Coast - Marine Exploration"
      - Holograph and typescript draft (Box 31, Folder 572)
      - Typescript outline, corrected, with research material, 1965-66, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 573)
      - Typescript outline, corrected, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 574)
      - Fragments. Typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 575)
    - "1805-1845."
      - Full title: "1805-1845. Overland Exploration. Claiming the Oregon Territory"
      - Holograph drafts, with research material, 1963, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 576-577)
        for George Davidson, Henry Eld,
        George Emmons, and Charles Wilkes
      - Typescript outline, corrected, with research material, 1966, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 578)
      - Typescript outline, corrected, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 579)
    - "1845-1865."
      - Full title: "1845-1865. Preparing for Trans-continental Union. Artists Associated with Government Surveys and Military Expeditions"
      - Holograph draft with research material, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 580)
      - Holograph draft and typescript, corrected, 1966, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 581)
      - Typescript outline, corrected, with research material, 1965, n.d (Box 32, Folder 582)
      - Typescript outline, corrected, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 583)
    - "1845-1865."
      - Full title: "1845-1865. Itinerant and Independent Artists Recording the Territorial Scene"
      - Typescript outline, with research material, 1965-66, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 584)
      - Typescript outline, corrected, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 585)
    - "1865-1885."
      - Full title: " 1865-1885. Part I. Hudson River School. Part II. Unaligned American Artists (Transition). Part III. The California-based Artists"
      - Typescript draft, corrected, with holograph notes, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 586-588)
      - Typescript drafts, corrected, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 589-590)
    - "Canadian Artists 1865-1885"
      - Typescript draft, corrected, with research notes, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 591)
      - Typescript draft, corrected, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 592)
    - Later Chapters, Covering 1885-1930
      - Holograph notes, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 593)
    - Biographical Sketches
      - Note: All biographical sketches are corrected typescripts
      - Index and list of reference sources (Box 33, Folder 594)
      - Abert - Anderson (Box 33, Folder 595)
        Agate, Alfred T.
        Alden, James
        Alden, James M.
      - Back - Bierstadt, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 596)
        Barchus, Eliza R.
        Best, Alice M.
        Best, Harry C.
        Bierstadt, Albert
      - Blakelock - Butman, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 597)
        Borglum, Gutzon
        Borglum, Solon Hannibal
        Brenner, Carl Christian
        Brewerton, George Douglas
        Browne, Belmore Haskell
        Browne, John Ross
        Burbank, Elbridge Ayer
      - Camfferman - Cram, 1960, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 598)
        Camfferman, Peter Marienus
        Chase, Albert W.
        Clarke, John
        Coleman, Edmund Thomas
        Collins, Caspar W.
        Colman, Samuel
        Colyear, Vincent
        Cooper, Astley David M.
        Coulter, William Alexander
        Couse, Eanger Irving
      - Dahlgren - Drummond (Box 33, Folder 599)
        DeCamp, Ralph Earl
        DeForest, Henry J.
        Dellenbaugh, Frederick Samuel
        Deming, Edwin Willard
        de Trobriand, Phillippe Regis
        Downing, Alfred
        Drummond, Sofie Theresa Pemberton
      - Eastman - Fulton, 1962, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 600)
        Eggenhofer, Nick
        Espey, Edward Lincoln
        Fairbanks, Avard Tennyson
        Farnsworth, Alfred Villiers
        Farny, Henry F.
        Fery, John
        Fisk, Elizabeth C.
        Includes letter from Lucienne
        Fery dated 1962 June 3
      - Garner - Gordon, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 601)
        Garner, C. L.
        Gegoux, Theodore
        Gibbs, George
        Gifford, Robert Swain
        Gifford, Sanford Robinson
        Glover, Eli Sheldon
        Gollings, Elling William
      - Gorham - Gustin, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 602)
        Graham, Charles H.
        Green, E.
        Greene, LeRoy
        Griset, Ernest Henry
        Grob, Troutman
      - Hall - Heywood, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 603)
        Hall, Cyrenius
        Hall, Robert H.
        Hanson, Hermann Wendelborg
        Harmer, Thomas Cooper
        Hart, Lance Wood
        Haseltine, Willian Stanley
        Heywood, Herbert
      - Hill - Huntington, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 604)
        Hill, Abby Williams
        Hill, Edwin R.
        Hill, Thomas
        Hind, William G. R.
        Holmes, Wiliam Henry
        Horsky, Emery D.
        Howland, John Dare
      - Innes - Jump, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 605)
        Innes, John
        Johnson, Frank Tenny
        Jonnevold, Carl Henrik
        Jorgensen, Christian
      - Kane - Korn, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 606)
        Kleiber, Hans
        Knowles, Joe
        Koerner, William Henry Dethlef
        Korn, Edward Meyer
      - Lamade - Lorenz, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 607)
        Lamade, Erick
        Laurence, Syndney
        Lazarus, Edgar M.
        Leonard, Nathan Frank
        Lillywhite, Raphael
        Lochrie, Elizabeth Tangye
      - MacLure - Mulvany, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 608)
        MacNeill, Hermon Atkins
        Magelssen, Nell Buretti Willard
        McMurtrie, William Birch
        Meyer, Louis Richard
        Mitchel, Jessie Lincoln
        Möllhausen, Heinrick Baludin
        Mora, Jo
      - Nichol - Preuss, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 609)
        Nichol, Thomas Jeff
        Norling, Ernest R.
        Ostner, Charles von Hohenzollern
        Ottinger, George Martin
        Peale, Titian Ramsay
        Pickett, James T.
        Point, Nicholas
        Proctor, Alexander Phimister
        Preuss, George Carl Ludwig
      - Quigley - Schultz, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 610)
        Quigley, Edward B.
        Riesenberg, Sidney
        Rockwell, Cleveland
        Schaeffer, Harry
      - Shirlaw - Swift, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 611)
        Smith, DeCost
        Stein, Aaron
        Stobie, Charles Stewart
        Stringer, Arthur Robert
        Stuart, James Everett
        Swan, James Gilchrist
      - Tappan - Woodbury, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 612)
        Toft, Peter Peterson
        Webber, John
        Wetteland, Sven Ofterdahl
        Whymper, Frederick
    - Other Papers
      - Book proposal. Holograph and typescript (Box 34, Folder 613)
      - "Illustrations." [Copy photographs, arranged by chapter, accompanied by correspondence and holograph notes], 1966-67, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 614-616)
      - Copy photographs, arranged by artist, accompanied by correspondence and holograph notes, 1965, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 617-618)
      - Permissions with copy photographs and other information relating to the illustrations, 1964-76, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 619-623)
      - Miscellaneous copy photographs, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 624)
      - Bibliography and acknowledgments card file (Box 35, Folder 625-627)